admanya.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy - Admanya.com

Overall privacy statement

We take your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, how we store it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the web site that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated directly by us.

1\. What information does admanya collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. Because we derive revenue mainly from third party advertising, collecting information is essential to keeping our services affordable to users.

We collect personally identifiable information when you provide it to us, such as when you post a review on our site, when you put a comment in our on-line forum or when you sign up (register) to use certain services. Several of the services that we offer on our site may require registration as a condition of use. Once you register with our site you are no longer anonymous to us. We may also receive information about you from other sources and add it to the information you provided to us.

This personally identifiable information is limited to:  
1\. First and last name  
2\. Gender  
3\. Date of birth  
4\. Home city  
5\. Occupation  
6\. E-mail address  
7\. Any other information that you may choose to provide voluntarily under "about me" during signup or subsequently while building your user profile

In addition to personally identifiable information, our web logs collect standard web log entries for each page served, including your IP address, browser type, page URL and timestamp. Web logs help us to diagnose problems with our server, to administer the admanya site, and to otherwise provide our service to you.

2\. How does admanya use the information?

We use the information we gather for four general purposes:

§ To customize the advertising and the content you see;  
§ To enhance the user experience in our site. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you;  
§ To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling users to participate in paid services, polls, contests, and forums;  
§ To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.

3\. How does admanya protect your privacy?

As a matter of policy, except where you have consented expressly, admanya does not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. However, admanya may share (read the next section to know more about information sharing) profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to members more targeted advertising, products and services. In such situations admanya will never disclose information that will be used to personally identify you.

To protect your privacy, admanya provides:

1 Email anonymization and relay to reduce 3rd party harvesting and spam;  
2 Password protected account information;  
3 Option to use nickname in public forums and postings;  
4 Limiting access to your information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel;  

Admanya doesn?t display your email address on the site under any circumstances.

However, Admanya has no control over privacy whenever a user voluntarily discloses personal information online for example on forum comments, through e-mail, or in review comment areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, the user may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

4\. How does admanya share the information?

Personally identifiable information

We will make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when:

§ We have your consent to share the information;  
§ We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process; or we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, Admanya?s User Agreement, or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our employees, our users, or others.  

Aggregate information

We aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes. We do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally.

Business transfers

We are always seeking to improve our web site and our business. In accomplishing these objectives, we may buy or sell a company, or one or more of the companies in our corporate family may merge with or be acquired by another company. If we sell a business, we may transfer some or all of your information as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue or for other business purposes.

5\. What information does admanya store?

Admanya stores the following information on a continuing basis:

1 All reviews and forum postings are stored in our database, along with personally identifiable information of users. The ads and forum postings may be stored even after deletion or expiry and / or may be archived elsewhere.  
2 Our web logs and other system related records are stored indefinitely.

Although we make good faith efforts to store the information in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public, we cannot guarantee complete security.

6\. What are my options?

Users who would rather not provide any of the user data requested by our sign up process do not need to sign up with us. You can still view much of the content and use many of the services offered by our site without registering.

We also give users the following options:

§ Opting to unsubscribe our electronic newsletters. Users who opt in may remove themselves from mailing lists at any time through the my account page or by following the instructions at the end of the e-mail they received from us;  
§ Opting not to provide certain personal information when you upgrade your membership, provided, however, that you may not be able to use some of our products or services without providing us with certain information.

7\. How can I review and update my personally identifiable information?

You can review, correct, or change the information collected during registration for our site. The instructions for doing this can be found in our my account area. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary. Users who are experiencing problems with our services or who have questions about how our services work can contact us using e-mail addresses at the bottom of this page. Currently, we do not offer users a way by which to completely delete personal information established at the time of registration. All account information is password protected.

8\. How will I know if the privacy policy is changed?

Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected first within this area of web site. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy statement.

9\. What is admanya?s practice regarding cookies?

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of our sites. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit most of our sites, although active participation in certain areas of our sites may require cookies. Cookies alone tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information, in which case we use the information to enhance your services in the ways described below. By adjusting your settings on your browser, you may elect not to allow cookies to be collected.

The information we gather through the use of tracking technologies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you.

We use and intend to use cookies and tracking technologies in a variety of ways, including:

§ Keeping count of return visits to our site or our advertisers' or partners' sites;  
§ Accumulating and reporting anonymous, aggregate (data collected in mass), statistical information on Web-site and advertisement usage;  
§ Determining which features our overall user population likes best;  
§ Saving your home city so you don?t have to select every time you visit our site;  
§ Saving your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site;  
§ Displaying the most appropriate advertising based on your interests.  
We allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on our sites and, sometimes, in our newsletters to use tracking technology on your computer. We do not give any personally identifiable information to them as part of this relationship. Unless you visit the Web site of these companies and provide them with personally identifiable information about yourself, these tracking technologies tell those advertisers nothing about who you are. Our advertisers' use of tracking technology is subject to their own privacy policies.

10\. General

Admanya, or people who post on admanya, may provide links to third party websites, which may have different privacy practices. We are not responsible for, nor have any control over, the privacy policies of those third party websites, and encourage all users to read the privacy policies of each and every website visited.

By visiting our web site and providing us with data, you acknowledge and agree that due to the international dimension of admanya we may use the data collected in the course of our relationship for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. In addition, please understand that such data may be stored on servers located in India and / or the United States. By providing us with your data, you consent to the transfer of such data.

Questions, Comments

We welcome your feedback on this document. For questions and comments about our user agreement and privacy policy and to report any breach, infringement or violation, email us to legal@admanya.com.
